<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ALESSANDRO RONCA on Alessandro Ronca</title>
    <link>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ALESSANDRO RONCA on Alessandro Ronca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>https://inspiredlabs.co.uk</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:14:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/overview/</guid>
      <description>Cerftified Wim Hof Method Instructor I teach people to improve their life circumstances. Now a Cerftified Wim Hof Method Instructor based in Italy, I have been practicing for several years. Courses take place around Il Parco dell’ Energia Rinnovabile, which is in Umbria, Italy. What is The Wim Hof Method? The Wim Hof Method is a tool to help manage health. It moderates immune response, connects you directly to nature and has been know to bring symptoms into remission.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Science</title>
      <link>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/science/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 10:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/science/</guid>
      <description>Scientifically how does The Wim Hof Method really work? Using empirical evidence built up over decades, The Wim Hof Method has proven to have numerous benefits. Wim Hof challenged doctors, and became the subject of ground-breaking research into the body&amp;rsquo;s natural healing capability.
Formal study into Wim Hof began in 2011 at The University Medical Center St. Radboud, Nijmegen, Netherlands.
From then on the numerous health benefits of cold exposure and meditation have started to be understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathing Practice</title>
      <link>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/breathing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alessandroronca.netlify.com/posts/breathing/</guid>
      <description>    Photo of Wim Hof explaining Breathing Practice.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>